<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyGymBuddy</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_youtube_playback">youtubePlayback</string>
    <string name="playerview_text">This is a YouTubePlayerView!</string>
    <string name="error_player">There was an error initializing the YouTubePlayer (%1$s)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_youtube">youtube</string>
    <string name="instructions_paragraph">If you walk up to any machine at this GYM I can give you some tips on how to work out properly. </string>
    <string name="instructions_title">Instructions</string>
    <string name="squat_text">Squat Press</string>
    <string name="bench_text">Bench Press</string>
    <string name="readme">This app will generate notifications about the region state
        even if the app is killed.
        The app will also auto-launch in the background on boot.</string>
    <string name="squat_instructions">Stretch and warm up. Place your feet no more than shoulder-width apart.
     Point toes slightly outward. Place bar over your trapezius muscle, not your neck. Grab bar
    about 6 inches from shoulders. Dismount weight and step forward (or backward depending on
    setup). Keeping your back straight, bend at your knees as if you were sitting into a chair.
    Keep your heels on the floor. Bring your thighs parallel to the floor for full range of motion.
    Thrust your hips forward, keep your lower back in a neutral position(slightly arched) and
    abs in. Use your whole body to assist in lifting the weight.</string>
    <string name="bench_instruction">Stretch and warm up. Keep your feet flat on the ground, about shoulder width apart,
        and keep your shoulders touching the bench. Use a wide grip for emphasis on pectoral
    muscles, narrow grip for emphasis on triceps, and normal grip(slightly more than shoulder width)
    for a balance of both. Do not bend your wrists or bounce the bar off your chest. Dismount the
    bar and control the weight until it is slightly above your sternum. Then, with control, explode
    the bar up. That is one repetition. </string>
    <string name="action_setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>

</resources>
